Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Ikolab.
I'm Ohana.
I'm Maika Sasaki
I'm Yori Noguchi
I'm Ana Yamamoto
Yay!
Today's project is
Disney 1st
Yamamoto
Yay!
This time it's a battle to finally decide who will be the leader of the Ikora club, Yamamoto!
Thank you!
The leader of Ikola!
I am the leader!
I'm, you know, I've been participating in all the big projects so far.
So far, 5 volumes!
That's great!
You're a pro!
I have 5 volumes!
I have a feeling these three are the ones I'm going to be playing with in private.
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, man!
I'm gonna do my best!
I'm on it! I got all the answers right!
I've never been a reader.
I've had zero, so I'm out a lot.
Well, looking back on it so far...
I'm Otani, Noguchi, Otoshima, Takamatsu, Kiya...
Kiya.
Takamatsu, Hitomi, Rao.
I'll take care of Kiya.
I'll take Kiya
And Sasaki.
And you take care of Morohashi.
I see.I see.
That's funny.
You don't know anything.
But Anna will be fine.
Please, today.
We're on YouTube together, too.
Let's do it!
We'll do our best!
That's the first question! If you could have one wish come true, what would it be?
What?
Why?
Are you talking about Anna herself or about Equal Love?
Equal love.
Wow, wait, that's Anna-esque, isn't it?
Oh my God, isn't it too soon?
I've never said it before.
Oh, God!
I didn't say "already" the first time.
You didn't say "first time"?
No, I didn't.
It's not tiny.
I didn't! You can't talk to the king like that.
No, you're not going to be king. One of us will be king.
Oh, I see.
Too bad.
You'll never be king.
Oh, my God, I just said that.
It's okay. I can cut it out.
Okay, here we go. Ready?
Ta-da!
One by one.
We'll stand on the Taisho Dome.
Standing up?You think it's going to stand up?
I don't think so.
That's what I want.
I want to laugh with everyone all the time. I want to be happy.
I want to be happy
That's possible
I want to
Stand in Taisho Dome with everyone
That's the way to do it
Then let's see if we know the right answer
I'm counting on you
Let's see...
How old should I be?
I'll be about 80.
To play with all the Equal Love people.
Ehh...
I'm the closest.
I want to be with you all.
It says "forever" on it.
Thinking about YouTube with the age difference
Laughing through our noses and
Laughing
The closest to the answer that came out was Mai ka
This is the point
0.5
But, you know, wanting to be together is different.
I want to be with you. It says "forever.
Always means together.
It's not the same thing.
Stop fighting for me.
All right, all right, all right.
(laughs)
Let's see.............for the kanai and the iyi
0.3 points0.3 point
How is it 0.5 points?
Yay!
I'm not convinced.
Okay, let's move on.
Next question.
What is your member's petit baklos?
I don't know. It sucks.
But here we are.
It's very recent for me.
Recently?
I've been kind of fucked up.
What have you done?
In front of everyone?
I found out.
You found out?
As an idol
It's unbecoming.
Unbecoming?
Can't be?
It can't be.
Okay, okay, okay.
I got it. I got it.
I got you.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it.
Curry of some magical kajiki burger.
That's it.
Put it on like that.
What?
Wait, I made a mistake.
Wait a minute!
I don't get it.
Ten points down, like that.
How much is that these days?
That way.That way.
What?
It's okay.
It's not unbecoming of an idol.
Not unbecoming?
You're not a tuna, are you?
It's unbecoming.
What do you mean "unbecoming"?
Three sexes, please.
All right.
In that order...
Too many members sitting with their legs open
Too many members are sitting with their legs open
I forgot my earphone
T-shirt inside out
Yes, I'm saying ah, so it's not
I'm sure.
Maika Ochimusha...
After we finished recording the other day.
Maika took off her makeup and everything.
When she came backstage...
she put all her hair up in front of her head like Ochimusha
And she had this much hair.
That's right.
It was like a bar.
You know?
And then you became Aleriki.
That's cheery.
They sent me a picture.
Here's the correct answer.
It's called Bakuro.
How about...
I'm here to eat muscats.
I'm here to train.
That was yesterday!
Yesterday!That was yesterday.
You're right.
But I'm in better shape than you.
You're so naive, you know that?
I don't give a damn about your sense of style.
What?
Not the point.
Third question.
Go ahead.
What's the last thing you couldn't stand?
When you made that picture...
It's true.
I wanted to.
If it was a sheet, would you talk?
Lilah kiss.
Not now.
Oh, no.
It was a seat.
You're talking about a sheet?
I don't understand.
It's not funny.
It's silly?
Yeah, it was.
He couldn't resist this.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Is it sad?
I wrote it, but I don't know what it means.
Patience.
I don't understand what you mean by not being patient.
Patience?
I don't know what that means either.
Maybe it fits.
Maybe it's right.Maybe I'm right.
Let's do it.
clap!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Same.
No, no, no, no, no.
You fell, didn't you?
Like that?
I fell down by myself in the middle of nowhere.
It was embarrassing.
But?
The look of pain on your face...
I couldn't help it.
I did it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Well, I'll get right to it.
Ouch face
Everyone answered correctly.
Yay!
Yesterday!
I don't remember anything before yesterday.
How many points is this?
One point two.
One and a half.
1.3
Wow, it's Kim, isn't it?
Kim, but this is only the third question.
Okay, let's go to the next question.
DODON!
What do you like best about yourself?
Hmmm...
I wonder.
I don't hear him talk about it much.
Favorite part?Favorite place?
Favorite place?
The outside?
Inside?
What's inside?
Finally.
He's the best at it.
What?
Your past self.
You like it?
I love it.
You're the one who'll go with me the most.
Kirara?
Okay, let's go. Ready?
Ready?
Good at goofing around
Good at shopping
Likes to joke around
Hey!
Oh!
Oh, I see.
It's good, right?
When you said you'd go out with me.
I see.
I wondered...
You're right, you're right.
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
Over here!
Do-don-don-don!
(electric) power
It's not here.
What?
What is it now?
You had that bitter look on your face.The look on his face when he ate something bitter.
The part where he remembers his childhood.
Aah!
Isn't that too close?
Close!
You're a good shopper.
You're so good.
Do you think it's right?
Maybe it's not.
Am I right?
It's not right.
It fits.
There's something in my hand.
It's taller.
0.5.
What is 2.5?
Yes!
So it's 1.8?
What do you mean, 1.8?
We've been overtaken.
This is where your downfall begins.
Was it really that important?
Let's move on.
Describe your favorite character.
This one's easy.
Wait, wait, wait, I can't write it.
Maybe I can't write it.
I can say it in my head in two words right now.
Ready? Okay.
Cinnamon.
Uma!
Um... Um...
Um... um...
Horse!
Mayka.
Wait, it says "bath" on it.Wait, it says "bath" on it.
I have a bath written down.
It's this way, right?
It's definitely this way.
The correct answer is this way.
It says "cute." Cinnamon.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's definitely Cinnamon.
It's just like a panda.
Cinnamon!
But I'm glad Maika and Yori were able to get that far.
Two points for you.
I'll give you 10 points.
Hana-chan, 15...
Um... um...
Ten. One point.
We're only one point short.
But there's a difference.
Next question, please.
Say something like Pucho Hensar.
What's Pucho Henzer?
Hands up, Pucho Henzer!
You gave me a hint...
You got a hint?
A member said...
He was like...
I was like...
What?
The first time?
Not that one.
Is it ever?
What the hell is that?
I know I know, but I don't know.
I'm not trying to be stubborn.I'm not being coy.
You really know what you're doing.
I know you do.
I know, but...
So what?
So it doesn't mean anything at all.
Okay.
Come on!
Pre-prepared cells.
And?
A small mole.
But I'm pretty sure it's not a petite mole.
It's a big pouch.
What's a puke?
Not "puké", "pugé".
That's a pudge.
I don't know what a pudge is.
I'm talking about chige.
The correct answer is this.
Say something like "pucho henza." Push mole.
Micah spare me!
But you're the only one here who noticed this mole of mine.
I noticed it just now.
I got some kind of mole on my hand.
Netsu Tenkoku
I was using it, and when I closed it for the last time, it just popped off.
But I used it to push the mole.
Did you notice the mole?
I thought "Oh shit" when I said "Micah".
He had a "oh shit" look on his face.
Don't touch it.
I thought, "Oh, shit.
I wanted to wash it off my face.
Micah's kindness came out.
Micah got 0.5 points.
Yay!We did it!
We won, didn't we?
Next question.
Is there anything you'd like to apologize to your manager for?
It's personal.
I know about your car.
I know you didn't do this.
I haven't done this yet.
I knew this.
I don't know this
Yes, I know.
Here it is.
I think it's time for you to give me some answers.
I'll be honest, Mom.
What if I use this?
Tell me you didn't do it, and this is the only thing that comes to mind.
I can't do this anymore.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I just saw the look on your face.
Yeah, you did.
I don't know.
Good luck, Hannah.
Okay.
I haven't sent in my YouTube project proposal yet.
I haven't sent in the survey on what I want to do.
Answer the questionnaire.
Aren't they great?
At the very end.
Let's take a look.
Isn't that a long time ago?
You asked me what I wanted to do on the Liko No Joy Channel.
But I haven't submitted the questionnaire yet.
I'm sorry.
You're right!
It was a long time ago!
It was a long time ago.That was a long time ago.
It was a long time ago.
I haven't submitted it either.
Next question.
Well, well, well!
I have something to say to Maika Sasaki.
What?
I'm flattered.
I'm happy, but?
Maika's been saying that to me a lot lately.
What I say to women?
You say that a lot.
It's all I have.
What? I don't know!
Let's set a time.
Ready.
What?
That's all you've ever said.
That's not limited to Maika.
I'll say it myself.
No, you're not.
Maybe you're right, but...
Are you marrying a woman?
Let me say it just once.
That, too.
Here you go.
I don't know why you keep asking me to go out for popcorn.
I don't know.
I do.
I want popcorn.
He's always asking me to go eat popcorn instead of going to the movies.
That's right.
It's okay... from Onomothmac, of course.
Next question.
If you're going to say "C," I'd like you to fix it for Oobahana.If you say "C", I'd like to see it fixed for big leaves and flowers.
I'd like you to fix the flowers.
There's more than Noguchi.
I'm fixing it.
Why the hell not?
That's why.
I want you to fix it.
I changed it.
I changed it to what I want you to fix.
I don't know why I'm not happy about it.
Lately
It's very recent.
But maybe it's because everyone knows it's more likely to be you.
Is it you?
Me? No, but it doesn't matter.
No, but it doesn't matter.
I'm sorry.
I apologize first.
I wasn't trying to guess, Mayuka.
I'm curious.
I'm just...
I'm worried about you.
Seino.
What?
Who's that from?
You left your socks on.
I don't get it.
You know, there was a pair of socks on the lesson table.
I don't know who it was from.
It wasn't me.
It's just bad publicity. I don't know.
Like maybe it was Iori who did it.
Because of your usual image.
It's a bad image.
Yesterday, when Anna and Hana disappeared.
There was a time when Milina and I and Iori were there, on top of the lesson.There was a time when Mirina and I and Iori were there, on top of the lesson.
And Iori was watching the video and laughing the whole time.
She's like, "Is that really possible? She said something like...
I said, "What? I said, "What?
She showed me.
And he's been laughing and talking by himself for like 10 minutes.
I've been laughing and talking by myself for about 10 minutes.
What's this?
I thought to myself.
You're right. You're alone a lot.
Maybe too much.
It's so big.
It makes you wonder if he's talking to you.
I've been made to feel that way.
I'm sorry.
Yes, don't leave the salad chicken out.
Hannah's mad at me.
What's next? Here you go.
Socks in the backstage area on top of the lesson.
Throwing the socks around.
Me?
But now that I hear this.
I thought you weren't Iori.
No, but there's a reason.
There's a reason why I chose Iori.
Chiara was with me when it happened.
I threw two of them out.
So Anne said, "Who is it? Anne said.
And Kiara said, "Sorry.
I said, "Me and Iori.
Wait, it's me!
I'm sorry.
Oh, wow!
It's me!
Oh, my God!Oh, great!
Wait, there's a good reason for that.
I had to run an errand.
I had to take off my socks
I had to take off my socks and put on these sandals.
So I made a declaration.
I put my socks right here.
I'm going home with them.
I told him to watch me.
I forgot about it.
Because it was there the next day.
It was at the entrance.
The blue one, the blue one.
One of them is Chiara.
The pink one is Chiara and the blue one is me.
But those socks are in my bag right now.
Then give me something to stand on.
No!
He just left them there.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
That's why Hana-chan gets 1 point.
Not even a princess.
How many more questions?
One more.
Oh, no!
Let's go!
Last question.
Here you go.
What would you like to ask Orb Hana?
A favor?
Well, that's a tough one.
I mean, the character of the flowers is what makes it work.
Is it doable?
I could do it.It's done.
I draw fast!
Moooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
It doesn't matter if it's right or wrong.
It doesn't matter.
Inspiration?
Flutter.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What the fuck?
Sorry. Sorry.
That was fun.
Yes, it's done!
It's done.
Please, guess who!
Let's have a school festival.
Treat me like a princess.
I want to be the cool older sister.
I want a low voice.
I'm sure there's someone in here who's right.
Let's see who it is.
That's me.
I want to dance and be called a princess.
So, Mai, you're right.
How did you know? How did you know?
Let's have a party.
I want to have a party.
I want to have a culture festival.
Let's have a culture festival.
Let's see the final result!
please!
more than 12.8 points
Maika 14 points
Hana 14.8 points
What a disappointment!
Maika, that was so close!
so closeIt's too bad
I knew he was no match for the champion.
Yamamoto!
That's great!
Six points.
That's great.
That's more than half.
We'll never get through it.
Kangri...
Well, I'll do my best to get over next time.
Over will do his best.
I'll do my best, sir.
Congratulations!
And that was the first Yamamoto.
Thank you very much.